W. R. "Bob" Poage U.S. Government papers, Inclusive: 1912-1981, undated, Bulk: 1960-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
W. R. "Bob" Poage U.S. Government papers
Inclusive: 1912-1981, undated, Bulk: 1960-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
1C
Poage, W. R. (William Robert), 1899 - 1987
148 document boxes and 1 oversized box.
This collection contains correspondence, reports, and other materials accumulated by U.S. Representative Bob Poage while in office from 1937 to 1978. The materials were produced outside of Poage’s duties with the House and pertain to other U.S. government entities including the White House, the Supreme Court, and various agencies and departments.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
William Robert “Bob” Poage, the son of William Allen Poage and Helen Wheeler Conger, was born on December 28, 1899, in Waco, Texas. The Poage family moved to Throckmorton County shortly thereafter, where William A. Poage worked as a rancher and cattleman. The Poages eventually returned to Waco in 1913. Five years later, in 1918, Poage graduated from Waco High School and joined the U.S. Navy as an apprentice seaman during the waning months of World War I.
After the war, Poage briefly attended classes at the University of Texas and the University of Colorado at Boulder before enrolling at Baylor University. In 1921, he graduated with a bachelor’s degree in Geology. Poage taught geology from 1922 to 1924, while simultaneously working on his law degree. In 1924, he earned his law degree from Baylor University and gained admittance to the Texas Bar.
In that same year, Poage ran for political office, winning a seat in the Texas House of Representatives. He served in the Texas House from 1925 to 1929, all while practicing law in Waco and teaching at Baylor Law School. In 1928, Poage attempted but lost a bid for a seat in the Texas Senate and briefly returned to civilian life. In 1931, Poage sought to fill a Senate seat vacated by Edgar Witt. He won the special election this time, ultimately serving in the Texas Senate from 1931 to 1937.
Striving to increase his political influence, Poage tried to unseat U.S. Representative O. H. Cross of the 11th Congressional District of Texas. Poage lost in 1934, but succeeded in defeating Cross in 1936. It was to be the start of a long-tenured career for the Texas Democrat. On February 14, 1938, amidst his political successes, Poage married Frances Lenoir Cotton.
Poage served in the U.S. House from 1937 until his retirement in 1978, often running unopposed in the biennial elections. Drawing from his childhood experiences and education, Poage championed life in rural America, seeking improvements such as water and telephone services and helping to establish the Rural Electrification Administration. Often referred to as “Mr. Agriculture”, Poage was a key member of the House Agriculture Committee from 1941 to 1978, chairing the committee from 1967 to 1974. Upon his retirement from the House in 1978, Poage was succeeded by Democrat Marvin Leath.
The W. R. Poage Legislative Library was opened in September 1979 in honor of Representative Poage and serves as the repository for his personal and congressional papers. Poage wrote five books during his lifetime including three in retirement: After the Pioneers (1969), Politics-Texas Style (1974), How We Lived (1980), McLennan County Before 1980 (1981), and his autobiography, My First 85 Years (1985).
Poage passed away during open-heart surgery in Temple, Texas, on January 3, 1987, and is buried in Waco’s Oakwood Cemetery.
Scope and Content
The chronology of this collection extends from 1912 to 1981, although the vast majority of materials fall within the years Bob Poage served in the U.S. House of Representatives (1937-1978). The materials, primarily correspondence and government publications, were produced outside of Poage’s duties with the House and pertain to other U.S. government entities including the White House, the Supreme Court, and various agencies and departments in the Executive Branch.
Series I. Agencies, Boards, and Commissions reflects the diverse nature of the federal government. This series consists primarily of materials such as correspondence, press releases, publications, and reports that Representative Bob Poage received from members of various entities such as the General Services Administration, the Postal Service, and the U.S. Supreme Court. Most materials in this series are from the 1970s.
Series II. Departments is the largest series in the collection. Materials in this subseries are divided according to the relevant department of the executive branch to which they pertain. There are twelve subseries in total: the Departments of Agriculture, Commerce, Defense, Energy, Health, Education, and Welfare, Housing and Urban Development, Interior, Justice, Labor, State, Transportation, and Treasury. The largest subseries is the Department of Agriculture, which reflects Bob Poage's legislative focus as a member and chair of the House Committee on Agriculture.
Series III. Executive, the smallest series in the collection, pertains to the executive branch of the United States government. The White House and its Office of Management and Budget are prominent correspondents in the materials. Representative Bob Poage received most of the following correspondence and press releases during the Richard Nixon, Gerald Ford, and Jimmy Carter Administrations of the 1970s.
Arrangement
The W. R. "Bob" Poage papers have been processed previously, most notably in 1995. Detailed finding aids and folder listings existed prior to this latest round of processing.
Due to the large size of the collection, the W. R. "Bob" Poage papers are being divided into six new collections based on the existing series outline. The materials in the U.S. Government papers were originally housed in Boxes #810-1089. Some loose materials have also been integrated with these files. The collection is now arranged into three series based on the original order: I. Agencies, Boards, and Commissions, II. Departments, and III. Executive.
Since Series II. Departments is so vast, it has been further divided into subseries based on the department the materials relate to. There are twelve subseries in total: the Departments of Agriculture, Commerce, Defense, Energy, Health, Education, and Welfare, Housing and Urban Development, Interior, Justice, Labor, State, Transportation, and Treasury.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 1C. Acquired 1961-08-01
Related Resources
Items in related collections
Mattie Mae McKee papers, Inclusive: 1940-2018, undated, Bulk: 1968-1991, 2008-2016
W. R. "Bob" Poage Campaign papers, Inclusive: 1898-1997, undated, Bulk: 1936-1978
W. R. "Bob" Poage State Legislative papers, Inclusive: 1923-1971, undated, Bulk: 1933-1936
W. R. "Bob" Poage Texas Development papers, Inclusive: 1913-1979, undated, Bulk: 1946-1978
Related references
Duggan, Laura Woolsey. “Poage, William Robert.” Handbook of Texas Online, accessed June 11, 2019.
Pearson, Richard. “Former U.S. Rep. William R. (Bob) Poage Dies.” Washington Post, January 4, 1987.
Poage, W. R. My First 85 Years. Waco, TX: Texian Press, 1985.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Poage, W. R. (William Robert), 1899-1987.
Subjects (Organizations)
United States. Air Force.; United States. Army. Corps of Engineers.; United States. Army.; United States. Department of Agriculture.; United States. Department of Commerce.; United States. Department of Defense.; United States. Department of Energy.; United States. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.; United States. Department of Housing and Urban Development.; United States. Department of Justice.; United States. Department of Labor.; United States. Department of State.; United States. Department of the Interior.; United States. Department of the Treasury.; United States. Department of Transportation.; United States. Navy.
Subjects
Agriculture -- United States.; Government agencies--United States.
Genres
Bulletins.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Government publications.; Press releases.; Reports.
- Agencies, Boards, and Commissions, 1912-1980, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  Series I. Agencies, Boards, and Commissions reflects the diverse nature of the federal government. This series consists primarily of materials such as correspondence, press releases, publications, and reports that Representative "Bob" Poage received from members of various governmental entities.
  The series is arranged alphabetically by name. Materials from the Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), the Federal Communications Commission (FCC), the General Services Administration (GSA), National Railroad Passenger Corporation (AMTRAK), the Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO), the Postal Service, and the U.S. Supreme Court are some of the most prominent in the series. Most materials were produced in the 1970s, Poage’s final decade of public service. Overall, the series is in good condition.
  - Agency for International Communication, “Reorganization Plan No. 2 of 1977” (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Bicentennial, Bicentennial Communities, Eleventh District, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Bicentennial, Bicentennial Communities, Eleventh District, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Bicentennial, Commemorative Events, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Bicentennial, Texas Day, Washington, D.C., Correspondence and Printed Materials, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission (ARBC), Correspondence and Literary Productions, 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Security Council (ASC), Correspondence and Report, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Architect’s Office, Correspondence, U.S. Capitol, 1967-1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Atomic Energy Commission (AEC), Correspondence, 1950-1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Energy Commission (AEC), Correspondence and Press Releases, 1962-1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Blue Cross and Blue Shield, Federal Employee Program, Correspondence, 1971 December 17 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), Correspondence, 1968-1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Airlines, Waco Orders, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Aviation Subcommittee, Statements, 1978 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Booklet, “The Civil Aeronautics Board Promotes and Regulates the Airline Industry”, circa 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Clippings, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Clippings and Printed Materials, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Clippings, 1968-1969, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Correspondence and Dockets, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Correspondence and Dockets, 1955-1958 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Correspondence and Clippings, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Correspondence and Dockets, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Correspondence and Clippings, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Correspondence and Schedules, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Correspondence, Dockets, and Schedules, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Correspondence and Dockets, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Correspondence, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Correspondence and Statements, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Correspondence, Dockets, and Press Releases (1 of 2), 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Correspondence, Dockets, and Press Releases (2 of 2), 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Correspondence, Clippings, and Schedules, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Docket, Southwestern Area Local Service Case, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Dockets, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Dockets, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), North American Airlines, Briefs and Correspondence, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Notices, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Pioneer Air Lines, Clippings, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Pioneer Air Lines, Correspondence, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Pioneer Air Lines, Correspondence, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Pioneer Air Lines, Dockets and Press Releases (1 of 2), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Pioneer Air Lines, Dockets and Press Releases (2 of 2), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Pioneer Air Lines, Resolutions, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Principles of Practice, 1951-1963 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Report, “Subsidy and Subsidy-Effect Programs of the U.S. Government”, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Reports and Statements, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Schedules and Station Data, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Schedules, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Texas International Airlines, Incorporated, Waco Area, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Texas International Airlines, Incorporated, Waco-Temple Service, Correspondence and Schedules, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Texas International Airlines, Incorporated, Waco-Temple Service, Correspondence and Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), Trans Texas Airway, Pamphlet, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Civil Defense Administration (FCDA), Brochures and Bulletins, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Civil Defense Administration (FCDA), Correspondence and Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Civil Defense Administration (FCDA), Correspondence and Press Releases, 1954-1957 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Civil Defense Administration (FCDA), Correspondence and Fact Sheet, 1959-1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Civil Rights Commission (CRC), Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Civil Rights Commission (CRC), Correspondence and Surveys, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Civil Rights Commission (CRC), Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Civil Rights Commission (CRC), Correspondence and Reports, 1974-1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Civil Service Commission (CSC), Civil Service Reform Act of 1978, Meeting Packet (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Civil Service Commission (CSC), Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Civil Service Commission (CSC), Correspondence, 1954-1962 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Civil Service Commission (CSC), Correspondence and Printed Materials, 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Civil Service Commission (CSC), Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Civil Service Commission (CSC), Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Civil Service Commission (CSC), Correspondence, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Civil Service Commission (CSC), Examination Materials, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), Clippings and Press Releases, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), Correspondence and Report, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Commodities Futures Trading Commission, Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), Report to Congress, “Improvements Needed in Regulation of Commodity Futures Trading”, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), Reorganization, Correspondence and Printed Materials (1 of 3), 1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Commodities Futures Trading Commission, Reorganization, Correspondence and Printed Materials (2 of 3), 1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), Reorganization, Correspondence and Printed Materials (3 of 3), 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Community Action, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Community Services Administration, Correspondence, Fact Sheets, and Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Community Services Administration, Correspondence and Reports, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Community Services Administration, Fact Sheets and Newsletter, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Community Services Administration, Grant Announcements and Correspondence, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Community Services Administration, Report, “State of Texas A-95 Review of Zavala County Economic Development Corporation”, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Consumer Federation of America (CFA), Newsletter and Press Releases, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Consumer Product Safety Commission (CPSC), Correspondence and Notices, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Consumer Product Safety Commission (CPSC), Correspondence and Press Releases, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Cost of Living Council, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Cost of Living Council, Economic Stabilization Board, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Cost of Living Council, Hospitals, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Cost of Living Council, Service Stations, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cost of Living Council, Steel Information, Fact Sheets, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Cost of Living Council, Wage and Price Controls, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Dallas Chamber of Commerce, Committee Rosters, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Defense Production Administration (DPA), Correspondence, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Defense Transportation Administration, Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Study Group, Reports, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Displaced Persons Commission (DPC), Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Displaced Persons Commission (DPC), Correspondence, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Displaced Persons Commission (DPC), Walter Bogus, Clippings, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Displaced Persons Commission (DPC), Walter Bogus, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Displaced Persons Commission (DPC), Walter Bogus, Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Economic Stabilization Agency (ESA), Clippings and Press Releases, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Economic Stabilization Agency (ESA), Correspondence, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Energy Research and Development Administration (ERDA), Clippings and Press Releases, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Energy Research and Development Administration (ERDA), Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Energy Research and Development Administration (ERDA), Legislative Materials, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Energy Research and Development Administration (ERDA), Printed Materials and Reports, 1975-1976, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Energy Research and Development Administration (ERDA), Statements, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Addresses, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Clippings, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Clippings and Press Releases, 1972-1977, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Correspondence, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Correspondence, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Correspondence, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Correspondence (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Correspondence (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Correspondence, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Correspondence, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Correspondence, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Draft of Compensation Regulations, 1978 September (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), “Environmental News”, Press Releases, 1970-1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), “Environmental News”, Press Releases, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), “Environmental News”, Press Releases, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Fact Sheets, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), “Federal Register”, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Grant Awards, Notifications, 1971-1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Guides for Committee Work, 1977 May (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Legislative Materials, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Newsletters, 1971-1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Noise Pollution, Leaflets and Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Order, “Initial Organization of the Environmental Protection Agency”, 1970 December 4 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Packet, “WaterELthe growth industry”, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Pamphlets and Public Laws, 1967-1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Pesticides, Clippings, Manuals, and Reports (1 of 2), 1973-1978 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Pesticides, Clippings, Manuals, and Reports (2 of 2), 1973-1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Pesticides, Notice, Endrin, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Pollution, Pamphlet, circa 1970’s (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Printed Materials, 1971-1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Printed Materials (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Printed Materials (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Printed Materials, 1976-1977, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Project Clearwater, Articles and Press Releases, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Publications (1 of 2), 1971-1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Publications (2 of 2), 1971-1978 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Resource Conservation and Recovery Act, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)